buyafollower.com 2011-12-09

# Privacy Policy, Buy Facebook Fans, Twitter Followers, Youtube Views, Google Plus Ones, Buyafollower.com

**Privacy Policy**

At [Buyafollower.com](http://buyafollower.com/) we take the privacy and security of our users very seriously. Please make sure to read and understand your rights and responsibilities when using our Site and Services.

 **  
1\. Policy Coverage**  
This policy covers all the Services provided by Buyafollower as laid out and explained in the [Terms](http://www.buyafollower.com/terms.php "Terms") and Conditions. If you need more detailed information in regards to our privacy policies, please do not hesitate to [contact us](http://www.buyafollower.com/contact.php "contact us").

 **2\. Customers’ Information  **  
In the event that you sign up for any kind of Buyafollower account, service, or promotion that requires registration, we will ask you for your personal information (e.g. name, email address and an account password).

For some services, like our advertising programs, we may also request credit, debit card, or any other payment account information.  We will maintain this information in encrypted form on secure servers which are operated by third parties such as [Paypal.com](http://paypal.com/) and Merchant accounts. We may combine the information you submit under your account with information from other Buyafollower services or third parties in order to provide you with a better experience and to improve the quality of our services. 

Your information will never be shared with any outside or unauthorized person or company. In some cases, we may give you the opportunity to opt out of combining such information.

 **3\. Information Recording Details**  
When you access Buyafollower Services, our servers automatically record information provided by your browser whenever you visit a website.

These server logs may include information such as your web request, browser language, Internet Protocol (IP) address, the date and time of your request, one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser, and browser type.

 **4\. Cookies**  
When visiting Buyafollower, we will eventually send you one or more cookies to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. Cookies are used to improve the quality of our service by storing user preferences and tracking user trends, such as how people search the internet.

Buyafollower’s advertising services may also use cookies to help advertisers and publishers serve and manage ads across the web. Buyafollower may set a cookie in your browser when you visit a website and view or click on an ad supported by our advertising services.

 **5\. User Communication Practices**  
Buyafollower may retain those communications (e.g. email or other communications) in order to process your inquiries, improve our services, and respond to your requests.

 **6\. Affiliated Websites**  
We may offer our services in connection with other web sites services. The personal information you provided to those sites may be sent to Buyafollower in order to deliver the service. Buyafollower process such information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. The affiliated sites may have different privacy practices and we encourage you to read their privacy policies.

 **7\. Links Tracking Optimization**  
In order to improve the quality of our search technology, customized content and advertising, Buyafollower may present links in a format that enables us to keep track of whether these links have been followed. 

 **8\. Additional Websites**  
This Privacy Policy applies to Buyafollower services only. Other sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you.  Buyafollower does not exercise control over the sites displayed as search results or links from within our various services.

 **9\. Collection**  
Buyafollower only processes personal information for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy and/or the supplementary privacy notices for specific services. In addition to the above, such purposes include:

 **a.**  Auditing, research and analysis in order to maintain, protect and improve our services;

 **b.**  Providing our services to users, including the display of customized content and advertising;

 **c.**  Ensuring the technical functioning of our network; and

 **d.**  Developing new services.

Buyafollower processes personal information on servers in the United States of America and in other countries. In some cases, we process personal information on a server outside your own country. Buyafollower may process personal information to provide our own services.

Also, we may process personal information on behalf of and according to the instructions of a third party, such as our advertising and affiliated partners.

 **10\. Information Sharing Policies**

Buyafollower only shares personal information with other companies or individuals outside of Buyafollower in the following limited circumstances:

 **a.**  We have your consent. We required opt-in consent from you for the sharing of any sensitive personal information.

 **b.**  Buyafollower provides such information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies or other trusted businesses or persons for the purpose of processing personal information on our behalf. Buyafollower requires that these parties agree to process such information based on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security terms.

 **c.**  Buyafollower has a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (1) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, (2) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (3), enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations thereof or (4) protect against imminent harm to the rights, property or safety of Buyafollower, its users or the public as required or permitted by law.

If Buyafollower becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will provide notice before personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. Please [contact us](http://www.buyafollower.com/contact.php) for any additional questions about the management or use of personal data.

 **11\. Security Measures**  
Buyafollower takes appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These security measures include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices.  In addition, we’ll include physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems and personal data.

Buyafollower restricts access to personal information to Buyafollower employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. These people are bounded by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations.

 **12\. Integrity**  
Buyafollower processes personal information only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this Privacy Policy or any applicable service-specific privacy notice.

Buyafollower reviews our data collection, storage and processing practices to ensure that we only collect, store and process the personal information needed to provide or improve our services.

Buyafollower takes reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we process is accurate, complete, and current.  Also, we depend on our users to update or correct their personal information.

 **13\. Information Updating Procedures**  
When you use Buyafollower services, we make good faith efforts to provide you with access to your personal information and either to correct this data or to delete it at your request if such data is not otherwise required to be retained by law or for business purposes.

Buyafollower asks users to identify themselves and the information requested to be accessed, corrected or removed before processing such requests. Buyafollower may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, or would be extremely impractical (for instance, requests concerning information residing on backup tapes), or for which access is not otherwise required.

Buyafollower will provide information updating services access free of charge, except if doing so would require a disproportionate effort.

 **14\. Enforcement Practices**  
Buyafollower regularly reviews its compliance with this Privacy Policy. Please feel free to direct any questions regarding this Privacy Policy or Buyafollower’s treatment of personal information by [contacting us](http://www.buyafollower.com/contact.php "contacting us").

When Buyafollower receives formal written complaints we will contact the complaining user regarding his or her concerns. Buyafollower will cooperate with the regulatory authorities to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that cannot be resolved between Buyafollower and an individual.

 **15\. Changes**  
This Privacy Policy may change from time to time. Buyafollower will not reduce your rights under this Privacy Policy without your explicit consent.  We expect most such changes will be minor. Regardless, Buyafollower post any Privacy Policy changes on this page.  If the changes are significant, Buyafollower will provide a more prominent notice.

 If you have any other questions or concerns regarding any part of this privacy policy, please feel free to [contact us](http://www.buyafollower.com/contact.php "contact us") through this website at your convenience.
